[ Cheering ]
[欢呼]
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; 好的
Welcome everyone.
欢迎大家
Welcome to our session
欢迎来参加我们的主题会议
connecting CareKit to the Cloud.
“将 CareKit 连接到 Cloud”
I'm Kelsey Dedoshka.
我是 Kelsey Dedoshka
And I'm our software engineer
是 CareKit 团队的
here on the CareKit team.
软件工程师
And so we'll start our session
那么 今天的会议将从
off today with a brief CareKit
CareKit 的简要介绍
overview.
开始
And then we'll introduce our
随后我会介绍我们
brand-new Bridge API where we'll
全新的 Bridge API
discuss in depth how to
并就如何将这个 API 整合到
integrate that API into a cloud
云后端
backend.
展开深入讨论
And in the process, we'll even
在整个过程中
dive a little bit deeper and
我们还会继续更深入地
walk-through understanding some
探讨对某些代码的
of the code.
理解
Then I'll invite Akshay up to
然后我会请 Akshay
the stage here to give you guys
上台来给大家做个
a quick demo.
快速演示
And we'll finish up by seeing
最后我们会看看
what you can all do with this
大家能用这个新特性
new feature.
做些什么
So let's get started.
那下面我们就进入正题
If you're interested in learning
如果你们有兴趣了解
what's new in the framework, you
这个框架中的新特征
can reference the earlier
还可以参阅先前的
session What's New in CareKit
主题会议“CareKit 和 ResearchKit 中的新特性”
and ResearchKit hosted by Sam
这是由 Sam Ravaka
Ravka [phonetic].
主持的
Or to learn how CareKit came to
如果大家想知道 CareKit 的诞生过程
be and its underlying
以及它的底层架构
architecture, I highly recommend
我强烈推荐你们
checking out last year's session
去观看去年的会议
talk Getting Started with
“CareKit 入门”
CareKit hosted by Omar Kahn
它是由 Omar Kahn
[phonetic].
主持的
Now since its introduction last
CareKit 自去年发布以来
year, CareKit has helped medical
已经帮助众多医疗机构
groups improve the overall
提高了病患医护的
quality of patient care by
的整体质量
providing at-home solutions for
它提供了家庭医护解决方案
tracking care activities and
以便追踪医护活动和
assessments.
评估情况
And allowing patients to take
此外  病患可以通过
more control over their care
各种 CareKit App  对自身医护状态
through CareKit apps has
拥有更多的控制及决定
presented new insights and
这给我们带来了新的洞见和
opportunities to take that care
机会 有利于更进一步地
and technology one step further.
提升医护质量和技术
And so this year we're
所以 今年我们要
introducing a new card for
介绍一种新卡片
patients to track care to-dos,
让病患可以追踪医护任务
like these stretches post knee
比如膝关节手术后的伸展运动
surgery, alongside some
以及他们需要完成的
assessments they may need to
一些评估活动
complete to track their progress
以便医生追踪他们在
along their care journeys.
医护过程中的进展
Now these adherence, symptoms,
目前这些坚持治疗的情态 个人症状
and outcomes are key data points
和治疗结果就是关键数据点
in understanding not only how a
它们不仅有助于了解
patient is feeling but how
病患的感受
engaged they are in their own
还能了解他们在
personal care.
自身医护中的参与程度
And data from this card is also
这个卡片中的数据
crucial for care teams to
对于医护团队而言也是至关重要的
understand whether their
这将有助于他们了解
treatments are having their
自己的治疗方案是否
intended effects or not.
达到了预期效果
Our CareKit Insights tab now
我们的 CareKit Insights 标签
features threshold alerts, which
现在添加了阈值提醒的特性
provides users with a nice
它通过窗口小控件  甚至是文本形式
visual indication via widgets or
给用户提供了一个很好的
even text that really bring data
视觉提示  这个文本实际上可以将数据
to the forefront of their
呈现在最能引起他们注意的地方
attention they may need to be
提醒他们需要关注
concerned about.
哪些事情
And last CareKit apps today
最后 现在的 CareKit App
allow patients to share their
还允许病患以 PDF 格式
data in PDF form via our Share
通过我们 Connect View 中的
Reports option on the Connect
Share Reports 选项  来分享他们的
View.
数据
And we found that it was time to
此前我们已经意识到  应该适时地
upgrade this share experience.
更新一下这种分享体验了
And so after the launch of
所以在 CareKit 发布之后
CareKit, we were excited to hear
我们非常高兴能收到
how valuable the data collected
通过 CareKit App 汇集而来的
via CareKit apps were, not only
数据 它们不仅对于病患而言弥足珍贵
to patients but to their care
对于他们的医护团队成员
team members.
也是如此
However, providing that data
但是 这些数据返回给
back to care teams is a manual
医护团队的过程  则是一个
process.
手动过程
And this can make it challenging
这会给医护团队远程升级
for care teams to update their
病患卡片
patient's care cards remotely
带来挑战
and even get a good sense of how
他们甚至很难正确地把握
they're progressing through
病患在医护过程中的
their care.
进展情况
And so these patient and care
所以这些病患与医护团队的 App
team apps really have to work to
真的需要努力改进
break down this data barrier
从而打破存在于彼此间的
that exists between them.
数据壁垒
And so we've seen some apps
所以我们看到了一些 App
create their very own backend
创建它们自己的
cloud solutions to help them
后端云解决方案
sync data between their patient
来帮助实现病患与医护团队 App
and their care team apps.
的数据同步化
However, this isn't an easy
但是 这并不是一件
task.
容易的事
And it really requires the
它真的需要
developers to handle doing a
开发者处理其中的
majority of the work.
大部分工作
They have to handle interfacing
他们必须处理如何与这些 App 的
directly with the apps data
数据存储器以及
store as well as with the
后端云系统
backend cloud system.
直接建立接口
And so we saw this growing need
我们可以看到
to help break down this data
越来越多的人需要打破
barrier and help patient and
这个数据障碍
care team apps securely sync
从而帮助病人和医护团队 App
data between them if they
安全地实现数据同步
desire.
如果他们需要这样做的话
And so this presented us with
所以这就给我们带来了
the opportunity to improve the
一个改进 CareKit 框架
CareKit framework by building
的机会
hooks directly in the framework
这种改进  是要在框架结构中
architecture so that current and
直接建立勾连 从而使得当前应用和
new applications can accomplish
新的应用能够以更简单
their data syncing needs in a
更清洁的方式满足它们的
much easier and cleaner way.
数据同步需求
And moving forward, we hope to
接下来 我们希望
improve the data pipeline with
能借助创建这个新特性
the creation of this new feature
来改进数据管道
and, in turn, reducing the
从而减少
required effort by the
开发团队
development team.
需要付出的努力
Now this cloud-based data
这种基于云计算的
sharing means patients who use
数据共享  意味着
CareKit apps at home to track
在家使用 CareKit App
their care can now share that
追踪自身医护情况的病人现在就可以
care data in real time.
实时分享这些医护数据了
And this is great because it
这一点很棒
allows their care teams to see
因为这就使得医护团队
their patient's results as
可以看到病患情况发展的
they're being recorded and gives
实时记录
them the opportunity to make
这样他们就有机会
adjustments in their care plan
对医护计划进行调整
or even to reach out directly if
甚至直接出面提供援助  如果他们愿意
they desire.
这样做的话
And so throughout this process,
所以在这整个过程中
we've been really inspired by
我们确实从许多
many CareKit apps, especially
CareKit App 里面获得启发 尤其是
the work being done at Sharp
南加利福利亚州
Healthcare in Southern
Sharp Healthcare
California.
所做的工作
And so let's create our own use
那么  让我们根据他们这些用户所给予的启发
case inspired by their users,
来发挥创造出我们自己的用途吧
for patients undergoing eye
我们来看看正在接受眼部手术的患者
surgery that takes advantage of
这项手术就利用了
our new CareKit features and the
我们的 CareKit 新功能和
Bridge API.
Bridge API
And it really showcases this
这真正展现出了
importance of data syncing.
数据同步的重要性
And so, in this case, the two
在这个例子中
weeks post surgery are crucial
术后的两周时间对于
to a healthy recovery.
病患康复来说至关重要
And patients must religiously
病患必须高度认真地
take antibiotic eye drops to
使用抗菌滴眼液
prevent infections that could
以防止感染
ultimately lead to blindness if
因为如果感染未能尽早处理
they're not treated early.
最后可能会导致失明
And then in our scenario here,
那么在我们的这个情境中
care teams can monitor their
医护团队可以监视
patient's results as they're
病人的情况
being recorded.
这些情况都会被记录下来
And if they aren't progressing
如果在他们的医护下
through their care, they can
病人情况并没有好转
make adjustments in their care
如果需要
plan if they need to.
他们可以调整医护计划
And patients can also see their
病患也可以通过 Insight 标签
eye drop adherence and their
来查看自己坚持使用滴眼液的
results via the Insights tab
情况和结果
and, again, so can their care
而医护团队也可以看到
teams.
同样的记录
Care teams can monitor their
医护团队可以监视
patient's results.
病患的情况
And if they aren't progressing,
如果病患没有好转
they can make adjustments in
医护团队可以
their care plan if they need to
根据需要来调整他们的医护计划
or even reach out directly if
甚至可以直接提供援助
they desire.
如果他们想要这样做的话
And so this use case really
所以这个使用案例确实
showcases this importance of
展现出了数据同步的重要性
data syncing and why we, as a
以及我们作为一个团队  为什么会觉得
team, found it so crucial to
着手整合出一个解决方案
begin integrating a solution.
是至关重要的事情
And so with that, I'd like to
讲完这些  下面我将为大家
introduce our brand-new Bridge
介绍我们全新的
API.
Bridge API
The Bridge API is an abstract
Bridge API 是一种抽象的
cloud API that conforms to the
云API 它遵循
CareKit schema and enables data
CareKit 方案 可以在
syncing without any additional
没有任何附加配置的情况下
configuration.
实现数据同步化
It's designed to allow CareKit
Bridge API 的设计初衷是为了
apps to seamlessly integrate
让 CareKit App 能够与
with backend cloud solutions.
后端云解决方案进行无缝整合
And it's built upon our current
它建立在我们当前的
CareKit data model and
CareKit 数据模型和
architecture.
数据架构基础之上
The Bridge API provides all of
Bridge API 为云解决方案提供了所有
the necessary hooks for cloud
必要的勾连
solutions to seamlessly hook
从而使得它们能够无缝接入
into the CareKit framework.
CareKit 框架
And this removes the need for
这样一来 就不再需要
third-party developers to dive
第三方开发人员来
deep into the code and extend
深入研究代码并
the CareKit framework to their
对 CareKit 框架进行扩展
specific needs.
以满足他们的特殊需要了
The API abstracts that away and
这个 API 把相关任务抽离出来
provides delegate functions for
转而为云解决方案提供了
cloud solutions to utilize
可利用的委托函数
And along with the Bridge, we've
连同 Bridge 一起 我们还添加了
added some additional UI modules
一些额外的 UI 模块
to make it even easier for
让开发人员整合和使用起来
developers to integrate and use.
更加的方便
So let's take a look at how it
那么就让我们来看看这是
works.
是如何操作的
Care plan activities are created
医护计划中的活动是用
using the OCKCarePlanActivity
OCKCarePlanActivity 对象创建的
object as either an assessment,
它或是一种评估 介入
an intervention, or even a
抑或是开发人员
custom type created by the
创建的自定义类型
These activities are then added
这些活动随后就会
to the OCKCarePlanStore via our
通过我们目前的 CareKit 框架函数
current CareKit framework
添加到 OCKCarePlanStore
functions.
当中来
Now this is where a Bridge API
这就是 Bridge API
really comes into play.
真正发挥作用的地方
It sits between the care plan
它位于医护计划
store and the cloud backend and
存储器和云后端之间
it listens to changes in state
会根据存储器中的状态变化
in the store.
作出反应
And when a change is detected,
当检测到变化时
the API reacts accordingly and
API 就会相应地做出反应
allows cloud solutions to pick
并且允许云解决方案收集
up those changes and sync the
这些变化
necessary data differentials to
继而在云端与存储器之间
and from the cloud.
对必要的数据差异进行同步
It interfaces with both the
API 与本地医护计划
local care plan store and the
存储器以及远程云端
remote cloud store to ensure
存储器形成了接口   从而确保
that any changes in state are
任何状态变化
handled accordingly.
都能得到相应的处理
Activities can be added,
它可以增加医护活动
removed, and updated.
还可以移除和更新医护活动
And the Bridge API hooks allow
Bridge API 挂钩允许
cloud solutions to pick up those
云解决方案收集
changes and perform the
这些变化并进行
necessary data syncing.
必要的数据同步
And as data is changed, updates
数据出现的变化
to the store pull down and
会被更新到存储器
stored in our local care plan
并保存到本地医护计划存储器当中
store to ensure the last data
从而确保最新的数据同步
sync is still available to the
依然是对用户开放的
user even if their device can't
即使他们的设备在此时此刻
connect to the cloud at that
未必能连接到
time.
云端
So let's take a look at how this
我们来看看
is accomplished.
这一点是如何实现的
You can continue adding and
你可以继续添加
removing OCKCarePlanActivities
并移除 OCKCarePlanActivities
just as you always have.
就像以前一样
And this means that no
这就意味着
additional configuration needs
你不需要对你现有的
to be made to your existing
CareKit App 活动进行额外的配置
CareKit app activities to
就可以利用
utilize the functionality of the
API 的功能
API and actively sync data.
并主动同步数据
But how does that actually work?
但这到底是怎么做到的呢
The API handles changes in the
API 会处理
care plan store by both
医护计划存储器中的变化
notifying the delegate when the
当活动列表出现变化
activity list has changed as
或者是当它收到事件更新时
well is when it receives an
API 都会
event update.
告知委托方
And these Bridge API hooks and
你们看见的这些
these methods that you see here
Bridge API 挂钩和方法
allow our cloud solutions to
使得我们的云解决方案可以
hook into this framework and
挂钩到这个框架
handle care plan store state
并且对医护计划存储器的状态变化
changes.
进行处理
And all of this happens behind
发生在幕后的这一切
the scenes to allow your CareKit
使得你们的 CareKit App
apps to access live updates in
可以获取
the care plan store.
医护计划存储器中的实时更新
And so these methods allow
所以这些方法使得
developers, like all of you, to
开发人员  比如你们所有人
build out your very own backend
能够创建你们自己的
cloud solutions that hook
后端云解决方案
directly into our Bridge API and
这些解决方案可以直接挂钩到我们的 Bridge API
that allow you to handle care
它们还让你能够处理
plan store state changes that
那些符合你期待的使用实例标准的
fit your desired use case.
医护计划存储器状态变化
However, if you're interested in
不过 如果你对使用
using a third-party solution,
第三方解决方案感兴趣
you can utilize one of the
你可以使用一个
existing solutions that have
现有的解决方案
already taken advantage of the
这个方案已经利用了
Bridge API and have available
Bridge API 并且还有
CareKit implementations ready to
现成可用 由 CareKit 执行
use off the shelf.
的解决方案工具
And so we've worked with both
我们已经与
Medable and CloudMine to help
Medable 和 CloudMine 进行了合作
them design and create HIPPA
以便帮助他们设计和创建符合 HIPPA 的
compliant backend cloud
后端云解决方案
solutions that use their
该方案使用了他们
existing HIPPA compliant backend
现有符合 HIPPA 的后端
cloud systems.
云系统
And utilizing one of these
利用这些解决方案当中的一种
solutions can help expedite the
会有助于加快
process of getting your CareKit
启动 CareKit App
app up and running with the
运行 Bridge API
Bridge API and actively syncing
和主动同步数据至云端的
data to the cloud.
进程
So let's take a look at one of
那么我们来看看
the existing solutions developed
其中一个由 Medable 开发的现成解决方案
by Medable and demonstrate how
并演示一下如何
to utilize the Bridge API hooks
利用 Bridge API 挂钩
to sync data with their cloud
来将数据与云解决方案
solution.
同步
And so here you can see how to
这里你们可以看到
start the client.
如何启动客户端
And this is going to reference a
这将引用
few necessary keys in your
你项目 plist 中的
project's plist to ensure that a
一些必要密钥  以便确保
connection can be established
能够建立一种连接
and data can be in syncing with
使得数据能够与
your provisioned account.
预先配置的账户同步
From there, you can login with
你可以从这里登录
your configured username and
用配置好的用户名和
password and proceed by either
密码登录 然后
handling the fault if there is
如果有错误 就继续处理错误
one or retrieving the return to
如果没有 就替该用户撤回
Bridge reference for that user,
返回给 Bridge 引用的信息
which you can use to be in
你在建立连接时
establishing connections.
可以用到这个 Bridge 引用
And once login has been
一旦登录成功
successfully established, the
云 Bridge 就知道要利用
cloud Bridge knows to utilize
这个账号来进行
that account for subsequent
后续的协议
transactions.
处理
And so once you've successfully
所以 一旦你登录成功了
logged in, you can list Medable
就可以列出 Medable
store connections.
存储器连接
And this will return the
这样就能够替那位用户
available connections for that
返还所有可能的
user.
连接
And these connections can be in
这些连接可能处于
a variety of states: accepted,
各式各样的状态 已接受
denied, or pending.
被拒绝 或者待处理
And so from there you want to
所以从这里开始你希望
handle connections accordingly
对这些连接都做出相应的处理
by either accepting pending
要么接受待处理的连接
connections or even grabbing the
要么为用户抓取
active connections for that user
活跃有效的连接
which you can use to begin
你可以利用有效连接
syncing data.
开始同步数据
Now it's really important to
这里有一点很重要
note here that data will not
确实需要注意 那就是
successfully sync to the cloud
除非你有一个有效连接
unless you have an active
否则的话
connection.
数据就无法成功同步到云端
And this is going to ensure that
有效连接可以确保
users only have access to data
用户仅能双向访问
to and from those that they have
他们已经授权的
authorized.
那些数据
And so denied connections will
如此而被拒绝的连接则会
prevent any data from syncing
阻止数据同步到云端
with the cloud and being shared
并阻止它与发起者
with the initiator.
的共享
And so now that we've looked at
现在我们已经介绍了
creating connections and
如何创建连接和如何通过 Medable
establishing them via Medable
解决方案而建立连接的问题
solution, let's take a look at
接下来我们来看
another new CareKit feature that
CareKit 的另一项新功能
utilizes these connections and
其中也用到了这些连接和
our Bridge API.
我们的 Bridge API
This new API opens the door for
这个新 API 不仅为同步
not only syncing CareKit data
CareKit 数据
such as activities and events,
比如活动和事件  打开了一扇大门
but it can be used to sync data
它还可用于同步
of other types as well.
其他类型的数据
And so a really great example of
这方面有一个很好的例子
this is secure messaging.
就是安全信息发送-
Secure messaging can be seen via
安全信息发送可以在
our Connect tab and showcased
Connect 标签里看见
using the new UI modules
同时 通过新的 UI 模块展示
developed in our latest CareKit
也就是我们在 CareKit 最新更新里开发的
update.
UI 模块
If you attended the previous
如果你参加了上一次的会议
session, What's New in CareKit
“CareKit 和 ReserachKit 的新特性”
and ReserachKit, you will be
你就会
familiar with the added inbox
熟悉这个通过
feature via the Connect tab.
Connect 标签添加的收件箱特性
Inbox provides developers with
收件箱让开发者
the ability to easily display
能够简单地
messages in a nice
以类似会话的良好格式
conversation-like format.
来显示信息的功能
And that messaging feature can
这种信息传送功能
be tied directly into the Bridge
可以被直接连接到
API and cloud backend solutions
Bridge API 和云后端解决方案
to allow patients and care teams
让病患和医护团队
to securely message directly in
可以直接在他们的
their CareKit apps.
CareKit App 中安全地发送信息
And so let's take a look at how
那么我们来看看
to accomplish this in the code.
怎么用代码实现这一点
Use the OCKConnectViewController
用 OCKConnectViewController
delegate the
委托以及
OCKConnectViewController data
OCKConnectViewController 数据源
source methods to set up your
方法来设置你的
messaging UI.
信息传送 UI
And please note that not all the
请注意 不是所有
necessary delegate functions are
必要的委托函数都在这里
showcased here, but we've chosen
展示 但我们选择性地
to highlight some of the more
突出了其中一些更为
specific methods.
具体的方法
And so this first method is
必须通过第一种方法
necessary to tell the delegate
告知委托
how many message items exist for
有多少信息条目属于
the corresponding care team
对应的医护团队
contact.
联系人
Patients and care teams could
病人与医护团队
have multiple conversations, so
可能会有多个会话 所以
knowing which messages go with
弄清楚哪些信息
which conversation will be
与哪个会话对应
crucial here.
在这里十分重要
And next you can implement the
接下来 你可以执行
connectMessageItemAtIndex
connectMessageItemAtIndex
function and return the
函数 并返回
appropriate message at that
该索引下的合适信息
An array of
一批 OCKConnectMessageItems
OCKConnectMessageItems can be
可以在你收发信息时
stored as you send and receive
被存储下来
And you can use the index
你还可以使用
property of this method to index
这个方法的索引属性来
into that array and return the
为那一批条目编入索引
appropriate message.
并返回适当的信息
And what this is going to do is
这一步是为了
it's going to allow your UI to
让你的用户界面
display these messages in the
以适当的顺序
appropriate order.
展示这些信息
And last you can implement the
最后 你可以执行
didSendConnectMessage function
didSendConnectMessage 函数
to securely send a message over
以便安全地发送信息
to your care team or over to
给你们的医护团队
your patient.
或者给你的病人
And so this is where our Bridge
所以这就是我们的
API and these backend cloud
Bridge API 和这些后端云解决方案
solutions really come into play.
真正发挥作用的地方
You can utilize those Bridge
你可以利用这些 Bridge
methods to either create a new
方法来创建一个
conversation or to even append a
新会话 甚至可以添加
new message to the existing
一条新信息
conversation thread.
到现有的会话进程中
And so let's see how that might
那么我们来看看
look using Medable solution.
它在 Medable 解决方案中是什么样的
So here you can see how to
这里你们可以看见
create the conversation.
如何创建会话
And this takes the message
这需要一个信息发送对象
object which can be created from
它可以从你的
your delegate properties and an
委托属性里面
array of targets indicating who
还有显示出这些信息该发送给谁的
those messages should be sent
一系列目标里面
to.
找寻出来
Now in this target ID property
现在  在这个目标 ID 属性中
you see of the target's
大家可以看见目标的
parameter will be the unique
参数是
identifier of the connection and
连接的唯一标识符
whom that message should be
也是该信息接收者的
sent.
唯一标识符
And success of this function
该函数的成功执行
will not only create the
不仅会创建
conversation but it will append
会话 还会
the attached message.
添加附加信息
It's really important to note
这里非常值得注意的是
here that we recommend not
我们不推荐
creating multiple conversations
通过这个 createConversation 函数
with the same connection via
来创建
this createConversation
具有相同连接的
function.
多个会话
Although it can be done, it's
虽然这可以做到
really best practice to create
但最好还是只创建
the conversation once.
一次会话
And subsequent messages should
随后而来的信息应该
be appended using the
通过使用 sendMessage 函数
sendMessage function.
来进行添加
And so this sendMessage function
所以这个 sendMessage 函数
is very similar to the one
与上面的函数
above.
非常相似
However, it takes the message
但是 它需要一个信息发送对象
object and now a conversation
现在还需要一个会话
ID.
ID
When you create the conversation
当你创建上面的会话时
above, it's important to keep a
有一点很重要
reference of that returned ID
就是要保留这个
which you should be using as the
被返回 ID 的引用
conversation ID parameter of
你应该会把它用作
this function.
该函数的会话 ID 参数
And this is going to ensure that
这样就可以确保
when you send a new message, it
当你发送一条新信息时
gets appended to your
它会被添加到
appropriate conversation thread.
适当的会话线程上
And for good user experience,
而且 为了提供更好的用户体验
it's also important to perform
还有一点也很重要 即
any necessary UI updates upon
执行任何必要的 UI 更新
creating a new conversation or
当你在创建一个新会话
even appending a new message to
甚或是将一条新消息
an existing conversation thread
添加至现存的会话线程
to ensure that your users are
从而确保用户能
going to get instant feedback if
收到即时的反馈
their messages were successfully
知晓消息是否
sent or not.
已成功发送
And so this messaging feature is
所以这个消息传送功能是
another great example of how our
另一个很好的例子 向我们展示了
Bridge API and these cloud
Bridge API 和这些
solutions are helping to improve
云解决方案是如何帮助提高
the at-home patient care
家庭病患医护
experience.
体验的
And so now that we've seen the
所以 既然我们已经了解到
architecture of the bridge API
Bridge API 的架构
and how to utilize it along with
以及如何将它和
the corresponding cloud backend,
相应的云后端搭配使用
I'd like to invite Akshay to the
我想邀请 Akshay 来到讲台
stage to give you guys a quick
给大家做一个快速的
demo.
演示
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt; 好的
Hello everyone and welcome to
大家好 欢迎观看
the CareKit Cloud Bridge Sync
CareKit Cloud Bridge
Demo.
同步演示
In this demo, we'll see how easy
本次演示中 我们将看到
it is to share data between a
在病患 App 和
patient app and a care team app
医护团队 App 之间
using a HIPPA compliant secure
使用符合 HIPPA 的安全
cloud bridge.
云桥接是多么简单
For this demo, we'll be using
在本次演示中 我们将使用
the OCKSample app which is
OCKSample App 它可以在
available Open Source on GitHub.
GitHub 开放源项目中获取
The OCKSample app is developed
OCKSample App 是由
by our [inaudible] team with all
我们团队根据现有的全部
the best practices in place.
最佳实践开发出来的
So we believe, for this demo,
因此我们相信 对于本次演示
the Sample app would be a good
这个 Sample App 将是一个很好的
starting point because anyone
起点 因为任何
who's familiar with CareKit is
熟悉 Carekit 的人
also very likely familiar with
很可能也熟悉
the Sample app.
Sample App
For more reference on the Sample
关于 Sample App 的更多参考信息
app, please refer to last year's
请查阅去年
WWDC session Getting Started
WWDC 的主题会议
with CareKit.
“CareKit 入门”
So let's see what the Sample app
那么 现在我们来看看
looks like right now.
Sample App 是什么样子的
On my computer here, I have two
在我的电脑里  有两个
simulators.
模拟器
In my iPhone simulator, we have
在我的 iPhone 模拟器上 我们装了
the Sample app.
Sample App
And currently for the Sample
目前为止 关于 Sample App
app, we have created and stored
我们已经在本地创建和存储了
a care plan store object locally
一个医护计划存储器对象
and an OCKCarePatientObject
和一个 OCKCarePatientObject
which is associated with this
它与这个医护计划
care plan store.
存储器相关联
There are three tabs: the Care
这里有三个标签
Contents tab which shows all the
“医护内容”标签 显示所有
activities that belong to this
属于该医护计划存储器中的活动
care plan store, an Insights tab
“见解”标签
which shows [inaudible] insight
显示所有相关见解的条目
items, and a Connect tab which
以及“联系”项目
shows OCKContacts that are
代表与患者的 OCKPatient 相关的
associated with this OCKPatient.
OCKContact 联系人
Explicitly for this demo, we
我们还为本次演示专门
have also created a Care Team
创建了一个医护团队
app.
App
On my iPad simulator, we have
在我的 iPad 模拟器上 我们有
the Care Team app which shows
医护团队 App  它显示了
the care team member and a list
医护团队成员以及
of patients that belong to this
属于该医护团队照顾的
care team member.
病患列表
Clicking on a patient will take
点击一位患者
us to their profile where we can
我们就可以看到他的主页
see their activities.
并从中看到他的活动
And for this demo, we're going
本次演示中 我们将
to show one of the patient's
展示该病患的其中一项活动
activities to show the data
并以此显示数据同步
syncing.
的过程
Currently, both the apps have
目前 这两个 App 都有
local care plan stores, so we
本地医护计划存储器 因此
won't be able to sync the data
我们无法在
between the two apps.
两个 App 之间同步数据
Let's go ahead and bridge this
接下来 我们使用云桥接
gap using the cloud bridge.
把这两个 App 连接到一起
Here's my Xcode workspace.
这是我的 Xcode 工作空间
And here are my two projects:
这是我的两个项目：
the Care Team project and the
医护团队项目和
OCKSample project.
OCKSample 项目
Let's go ahead and first add our
我们继续 首先将我们的
cloud bridge to our Care Team
云桥接添加到医护团队
app first.
App 里
And as Kelsey mentioned earlier,
然后 正如 Kelsey 提过的
we will be using Medable as our
我们将使用 Medable 作为我们
cloud bridge solution for this
此次演示的云桥接解决方案
So the first thing that you need
所以 你们要做的第一件事情是
to do is go to Medable's GitHub
去 Medable 的 Github
and download or clone their API
下载或复制他们的 API
into our project and then
用于我们的项目 然后
integrate the framework into our
将它的框架集成到我们的
project.
项目当中
I've already downloaded
我已经下载了
Medable's API and added the
并且 Medable 的 API 已经把
Medable's framework into my
Medable 的框架添加到了我的项目
project right here with all my
就在这里 这里还有我其他的框架
other like CareKit and
比如 CareKit 和
ResearchKit and all of the
ResearchKit 等各种
frameworks.
框架
To use Medable's API, we have to
要使用 Medable 的 API  我们需要
add some of their files.
添加一些他们的文件
We can do this by going to their
我们可以通过进入他们的
CareKit Bridge API folder and
CareKit Bridge API 文件夹 然后
dragging and dropping it into
将该文件夹拖放进
our project right here.
我们的项目 放在这里
Let's see what this directory
我们来看看这个目录里有哪些
has.
文件
It has three types of files.
它有三种类型的文件
First, all the helper files that
第一种 所有我们需要的辅助文件
we need which are Medable object
它们是 Medable 里相对于
counterparts of the CareKit
CareKit 对象的对象
objects, for example
例如
MDCarePlanStore,
MDCarePlanStore
MDCarePlanPatient, etcetera.
MDCarePlanPatient 等等等等
The second is the Medable
第二种是 Medable
[inaudible] Bridging Header.
Swift Bridging Header
Let's go ahead and add this
接下来 我们将该
bridging header to our project.
桥接标头添加至我们的项目
I'll go to my project and in my
我要在 Building 设置里
build settings.
打开我的项目
I look for the bridging header.
我查找桥接标头
And add the bridging header
并将该桥接标头
right here.
添加到这里
Perfect. Now we have added all
完美 现在 我们已将所有
the files that we needed from
需要的文件从
Medable into our project.
Medable 添加到我们的项目
The next thing that we have in
另外 我们在这份目录中
this directory is the care plan
拥有的另一样东西
store category.
就是医护计划存储器类别
This category has all the
这个类别具备我们
methods that we need to create
需要的全部方法
the Medable counterpart objects
有了这些办法  我们就能从 CareKit 对象中
from our CareKit object.
创建对应的 Medable 副本对象
To use Medable's API, we also
要使用 Medable 的 API  我们也
need to add a few necessary
需要将几个必要的方法
methods into our project.
添加至我们的项目中
We'll be adding those into our
我们将把它们添加到我们的
LocalCarePlanStore.m files.
LocalCarePlanStore.m 文件里
Let's first add those methods in
我们先添加这些方法
and then I'll talk about what
然后我再谈谈
those methods do.
这些方法的用处
In my CarePlanStore.m file, I'm
在我的 CarePlanStore.m 文件中
going to add those methods.
我将添加这些方法
And these methods will mimic
这些方法将会模仿
whatever the local care plan
任何本地医护计划
store methods do.
存储器方法所做的事情
For example, in our
例如 在我们的
CarePlanStore we have an
CarePlanStore 里 我们有一个
activity method and the methods
活动方法 而且我们
that we just added will do
刚添加的方法也要做
exactly the same but on the
完全一样的事情 只不过
Medable side so all of these
它们属于 Medable 在这个方面
methods are adding activity,
所有这些方法都在添加活动
removing an activity, updating
移除活动 更新
an event, etcetera.
事件 等等
With this, we have added
这样 我们就已经将
everything that we need as files
所有需要的东西都以文件
and code into our project.
和代码的形式添加至我们的项目
To use Medable's API, you need
要使用 Medable 的 API 我们需要
to create an account with them.
用它们创建一个账户
When you create an account, you
当你创建账户时
get three types of credentials:
你有三种类型的凭证
a client key, a base URL, and an
客户端密钥 基地址和
organization name.
组织名称
We have to add these three
我们要将这三种
credentials into our project to
凭证添加至我们的项目中
hook up our project to our
以将我们的项目与
account on Medable.
Medable 上的账户勾连在一起
Let's go ahead and see how to do
我们继续 来看看
that.
要怎么做
Go to your projects info.plist
进入你们项目的info.plist文件
file and create a dictionary.
创建一个字典
And we'll call it Medable, and
我们将它称作 Medable 然后
set it as a dictionary.
把它设置成字典
Now in this dictionary, we'll
现在 在这个字典里 我们
have to add three key value
要添加三个
pairs.
键值对
The first is the ClientKey.
第一个是 ClientKey
Second one is the BaseURL.
第二个是 BaseURL
And third is the Organization
第三个是组织名称
Perfect. When we add these three
完美  当我们添加了这三个
credentials, we should be able
凭证之后 我们应当能够
to link our project to our
将自己的项目连接至我们
account at Medable.
Medable 上的账户
We have to perform all of these
我们同样需要对我们的
steps for our Sample app as
Sample App 添加
well.
所有这些操作步骤
And for this demo, I've already
为了本次演示 我已经
added all of these steps into
将所有步骤添加到
our Sample app already.
我们的 Sample App
So now both of our apps are
所以现在 两个 App 都已经
having [inaudible] Medable and
设置好 而且
configured with the cloud
配置了云桥接
bridge.
云桥接
Let's go ahead and use those.
接下来 我们要使用它们
When we create an account with
当我们使用 Medable 的控制面板
Medable, with their dashboard,
在其中创建账户时
we should be able to create a
我们应当能够创建一个
care team member account.
医护团队成员的账户
And we can do that by providing
我们可以通过提供
an e-mail, a password, and a
电子邮件 密码和
phone number.
电话号码来实现
So when we create the care team
所以 当我们创建医护团队
member account, in return we get
成员账户时 作为交换 我们会获得
a verification token.
一个验证令牌
That verification token is
医护团队成员
needed by the care team member
需要用该验证令牌
to log themselves in.
登录自己的账户
And these properties can be
而这些属性可以
provided through the UI,
通过用户界面提供出来
preferably using the ResearchKit
最好是使用 ResearchKit 的
login step.
登录步骤
So let's go ahead and add those
所以 我们往下继续 再把那些内容添加
in.
进来
I'll go into my projects app
我要进入我的项目 App 的
delegate file.
委托文件
And first I will add all the
首先我将添加所有
necessary properties that I
我可能需要的
would be needing.
必要属性
Here I have a cloud bridge.
我在这里有一个云桥接
I'll talk a little bit in more
稍后我将
detail about this in a minute.
更详细地谈一谈它
The e-mail, the password, and a
谈谈医护团队成员的
verification token of the care
电子邮件 密码和
team member.
验证令牌
And then I'll get back to these
然后我会很快地回到这些
properties in a minute.
属性
Let's go ahead and add Medable's
接下来 我们来添加 Medable 的
login method.
登录方法
Here's the [inaudible] .login
这里是一个云桥接登录
method which takes an e-mail, a
方法 使用到了电子邮件
password, and a verification
密码以及验证
token.
令牌
If the person is successfully
如果这名用户成功
logged in, we should be able to
登录 我们就能够
create a patient.
新建一个病患记录
Otherwise, this method returns a
否则 该方法将返回
fault.
错误
Let's say the care team member
我们假设该医护团队成员
is logged in.
已经登录
Now we should be able to create
现在 我们应当可以从
a patient from here.
这里新建一个病患
And that's where these
这些属性的
properties come in.
来源就在于此
To create a patient, we need the
为了新建一个病患 我们需要
patient's first name, their last
该病患的名和姓
name, and all of their details
以及他们所有的详细信息
and their e-mail ID.
以及其电子邮件 ID
Let's go ahead and create a
接下来 我们用这些属性
patient using these properties
新建一个病患
adding the first name, the last
添加名字 姓氏
name, all of the properties of
以及该病患所有的
the patient.
属性
And this method does two things.
该方法将进行两项操作
In its callback, if we were not
在回调时 如果我们
able to create a patient, it
未能新建病患 它
returns a fault.
就会返回一个 Fault 值
But if you were successfully
不过 如果你成功
able to create a patient, then
新建病患 那么
the callback returns a bridge.
该回调就会返回一个桥接
Now this is the place where you
现在 这里是你能
can access the care plan store.
访问医护计划存储器的地方
So by doing [inaudible] cloud
所以 通过这一步骤
bridge is setting up a local
云桥接正在设置一个
variable, the cloud bridge, to
本地变量
the cloud bridge that we
对于我们从回调
received from callback, we have
接收到的云桥接 我们
access to the cloud bridge from
可以在 App 的
anywhere in our app.
任何地方访问这个云桥接
And that's what we can do
这就是我们使用
cloudbridge.careplanstore.
cloudbridge.careplanstore 所能做的事
It will give us access to the
它让我们得以访问
care plan store that we need.
我们所需要的医护计划存储器
We will replace our care plans
我们准备替换我们的医护计划
store and make the
存储器 并将通过 App 来把
cloudbridge.careplanstore as our
cloudbridge.careplanstore 作为
default care plan store
默认的医护计划
throughout the app.
存储器
The second thing that this
这个方法当中的
method does is sends an
第二件事情  就是把邀请令牌
invitation token to the patient
发送-到我们提供给病患的
in their e-mail which we
电子邮箱里
When the patient receives this
当病患收到这份
e-mail, they should be able to
电子邮件时 他们应该能够
register themselves through the
通过病患 App 来注册
patient app.
自己的账户
And they would need this
他们可能会需要
verification token which is sent
发送到他们电子邮箱
-- the invitation token that is
的邀请令牌
sent to their e-mail to register
来给自己
themselves.
注册账户
Let's go ahead and register the
接下来 我们在病患 App 上
patient in the patient app.
注册该病患
In my patient app, I'll go to
在我的病患 App 上 我要进入
the app delegate and add all the
这个 App 的委托 添加
variables that we need for a
我们在病患注册所需的
patient to register.
全部变量
This includes the first name,
这包括名字
last name, e-mail, their mobile
姓氏 电子邮件 手机号码
number, a password, and an
密码和
invitation token.
邀请令牌
And all of these properties can
而所有这些属性都能
be provided through the UI.
通过用户界面提供
Let's go ahead and add the
我们继续  现在我们要添加
method to register the patient.
病患注册时使用的方法
The register account method
注册账户方法
takes in the first name, the
需要名字 姓氏
last name, the e-mail, the
电子邮件
mobile number, the password, and
手机号码 密码和
the invitation token.
邀请令牌
And, again, in the callback,
而且 在回调时
returns the cloud bridge.
也会返回云桥接
This is, again, the same cloud
此外 这也是
bridge that the care team
医护团队成员访问的
members are accessing.
同一个云桥接
So if you do the
因此 如果你使用
cloudbridge.careplanstore, both
cloudbridge.careplanstore
the care team member and the
医护团队成员和
patient should be able to access
病患都将能够访问
the same care plan store.
同样的医护计划存储器
Make sure you save this cloud
请确保你将该云桥接
bridge in one of your variables
保存在你文件中的
in your file and make the
某个变量里面 并将
cloudbridge.careplanstore as
cloudbridge.careplanstore 设置为
your default care plan store
默认医护计划存储器
throughout the app.
通过 App  就可以实现这一点
When we do this, we have
当我们进行这样的操作时 我们
successfully made care team app
已经成功使得医护团队 App
and the patient app access a
和病患 App 能够访问一个
common care plan store.
共同的医护计划存储器
Now any activity or an update in
现在  在 App 里完成的
an activity which is done on
任何一项活动
either of the apps should
或者是更新
reflect on the other app as
无论是在两个 App 中的哪一个上面完成的
well.
都应该对另一方进行思考分析
Let's go ahead and test this
接下来 我们再来检验
out.
一下
For this demo, we have already
为了本次演示 我们已经
created a different version of
创建出这个 App 的不同版本
the app which has all the same
它的所有信息都相同
information but we have added
不过我们已经添加了
the login credentials and the
登录凭证和
organization name also to these
组织名称到这些
apps.
App 里面
In my iPhone simulator, I have
我的 iPhone 模拟器上有
the Sample app.
Sample App
And in my iPad simulator, we
我的 iPhone 模拟器上
have the Care Team app.
还有医护团队 App
The Sample app is just the same
Sample App 是同样的 App
app with all the login
它需要所有的
credentials needed.
登录凭证
And the Care Team app is also
Care Team App 也是同样
just the same app with all the
它也要求所有的
login credentials.
登录凭证
Let's go ahead and complete the
接下来 我们来完成
pain activity for today.
今天的疼痛活动
In my pain activity, I'm feeling
在疼痛活动中 我感觉
somewhere around, let's say
疼痛程度大约为七的时候
seven and I hit Done.
然后我就点击完成
And in no matter of time, this
而无论何时
activity should sync over the
这个活动都会将数据同步至
data to the care plan activity
医护团队的
on the care team side.
医护计划活动
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Now during the day, whenever
现在在白天里  无论何时
patients feel like their
只要病患感觉他们的
activity has changed, they can
活动有所改变 无论在什么时候他们都能
-- whenever they update an
更新活动
activity, it should also reflect
并会反映到
on the care team side.
医护团队这边
And the time that this is taking
而且所需时间是
is variable, which you can set
可变的 你可以
through the API.
通过 API 设置
If you wanted to, based on your
如果基于你的
use case, if you think the
用例 如果你想调整
frequency of your updates, you
更新的频率 你
can change this lapse and either
可以更改间隔时间 要么
increase it or decrease it.
增加 要么减少
With this data syncing, we have
有了这个数据的同步 大家在本次
seen in this demo, we took two
演示中已经看到 我们使用了
applications with local care
两个具有本地医护计划存储器的
plan stores and created a common
应用  并创建了一个共同的
cloud bridge and made both the
云桥接  并且使得两个 App
apps access the common care
都能访问这个共同的医护
plans store and share the data
计划存储器
across.
并且共享数据
We believe there was a very
我们认为像这样的
urgent need for functionality
功能是大家迫切
like this.
需要的
And with all of these resources
随着所有这些资源
being public, we cannot wait to
的公开 我们全体人员真是迫不及待地
collectively help thousands of
希望每天都能帮助数以千计的
people every day.
人们
With this, I would like to call
说到这里 我想请
back Kelsey up on stage and
Kelsey 回到台上
continue with the session.
继续本次会议
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; So thank you to Akshay for
&gt;&gt; 感谢 Akshay
that awesome demo.
演示得非常精彩
And so as you guys just saw, the
大家刚刚了解到了
process of getting a CareKit app
创建 CareKit App 的过程
up and running with the Bridge
还有调用 Bridge API 的方法都
API is fairly straightforward.
相当简单直接
You saw firsthand how the apps
大家亲眼见到了 App 是如何
sync data to and from the cloud
与云端往来同步数据
and how to utilize those bridge
以及怎样在这些
methods in these cloud solutions
云解决方案里
directly in your Xcode
在你的 Xcode 应用中
application.
直接使用那些桥接
And so throughout the session,
所以在整场会议里
we introduced the addition of
我们介绍了
the Bridge API to the CareKit
CareKit 框架里新增的
framework.
Bridge API
We discussed the architecture of
我们讨论了
how it works.
它的运行架构
And you saw how to utilize it in
此外 通过观看现场演示
the code along with viewing a
大家还了解了如何
live demo.
在代码中使用它
So what can you do with this new
那么  大家能用这个新特性
feature?
做些什么呢
The Bridge API not only
Bridge API 不仅
integrates with each of the
与每个现有的
existing CareKit modules but is
CareKit 模块进行集成
modular and easily extendable to
它还具有模块化属性  易于扩展
be used with new ideas and
来服务于开发者社区提供的
contributions from the developer
新想法和贡献
community like all of you.
就像在座的各位
And now that we all have a
现在 既然我们都对
better understanding of what the
Bridge API 有了更多的了解
Bridge API is, it's important to
我们很有必要
point out and recognize how
指明和确认
powerful this tool can be.
该工具能够有多么强大
It opens the door and provides
它向开发者 医护团队和
developers, care teams, and
医疗机构
medical institutions with the
敞开大门
technology that allow them to
为他们提供技术 让他们
care for their patients in a
以一种更私人和更投入的方式
more personal and engaged way.
照顾病人
But what do I mean by that?
那我想表达的是什么呢
It's great to see how CareKit
我想说 能够看到 CareKit
and each of its existing modules
和它现有的每个模块
is helping to improve the
帮助人们提升
at-home patient care experience,
病患家庭医护体验 实在是了不起
but it's even better if we can
但是 如果我们能够
involve their care teams.
让医护团队参与进来  那就更好了
To improve the patient care
为了改进病患医护的
process, we looked at this API
过程 我们关注这个 API
to help care teams get a better
并用它来帮助医护团队更好地
understanding of their patient's
理解病人的
needs and to get one step ahead
需求 从而让他们的医护水平
of their care.
进一步提高
And this can help provide
这能够给病患者
patients with a sense of
带来一种安心感
reassurance and encourage them
并且能够鼓励他们
to become more engaged in their
更加投入地
own personal care.
进行个人医护
And these are all powerful tools
这些都是很强大的工具
that now exist at your
现在它们就存在于你的
fingertips.
指尖之下
And what comes next is up to
接下来会发生什么  这取决于
you.
在座的各位
Whether it's extending your
无论是扩展你们
existing applications or
现有的应用 还是
starting from scratch, we
从零开始
believe that CareKit along with
我们相信 CareKit 和
the Bridge API and developers
Bridge API  再加上你们这样的
like all of you have the power
全体开发者 是有能力
to improve the at-home patient
提升病患-
care experience and decrease the
家庭医护体验的  并且缩小
patient care gap that exists
现存的
today.
病患医护差距
And so with this new
因此 有了这个新的功能特性
functionality, we look out to
我们着实期待
all of you to take advantage of
你们所有人都能利用
existing third-party backend
现有的第三方后端
cloud solutions or to build your
云解决方案  或是创建你们
own.
自己的云解决方案
And in the process, consider who
在创建过程中 要考虑一下
that data will be syncing with
数据将与谁同步
and how that corresponding care
而与之相应的医护团队 App
team app may look.
可能是什么样的
The Bridge API is only as
从另一方面来看  Bridge API
powerful as the care team app on
在创建医护团队 App 时
the other side.
也有同样强大的功能
And so we look to all of you to
所以 我们期望所有人来
help build out these care team
帮助扩建这些医护团队解决方案
solutions via care team apps and
通过医护团队 App 和
dashboards.
控制面板的形式
And CareKit is Open Source so as
因为 CareKit 是开放资源的 所以
you build out these solutions
当你创建这些解决方案
and improve your existing
完善你已有的应用程序时
applications, please contribute
请将这方面的工作情况
that work back so as a team we
转告给我们 这样 我们作为一个团队
can continue to evolve and grow
便可以继续演化和发展
the CareKit framework.
CareKit 框架
And so more information about
更多关于
CareKit and both the Bridge API
CareKit 的信息以及 Medable 和
solutions from Medable and
CloudMine 上的 Bridge API 解决方案
CloudMine can be found at the
都能在目前提供的
provided link.
链接里找到
And if you're interested in
如果大家有兴趣
learning more about CareKit or
想进一步了解 CareKit 或
its relating technologies,
与之相关的技术
please take a look at one of the
请观看以下会议的
following sessions.
任何一场
So thank you all for coming to
感谢大家参加本次
the session on the CareKit
关于 CareKit Bridge API 的
Bridge API.
会议
And we really look forward to
我们很期待
seeing what you all do with this
看到大家如何应用
new technology.
这个新技术